Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Novels (Box 1-83)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's champions or all in the game Series Title: Burt L. Standish Library Series Number: 19 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1320)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's return to Yale; or, welcomed home Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 20 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1321)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's secret or, right vs. might Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 21 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1322)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's danger or, saved by nerve Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 22 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1323)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's loyalty or, true to his friends Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 23 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1324)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell in camp or, fun in the open Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 24 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 65, Folder 1325)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's vacation or, getting back to form Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 25 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1326)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's cruise or, pleasure and peril afloat Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 26 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1327)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's chase or, excitement for everybody Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 27 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1328)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell in Maine or, the lure of 'way down east Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 28 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1329)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's struggle or, fighting hard for honor Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 29 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1330)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's first job or, bound to make good Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 30 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1331)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's opportunity or, a question of honor Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 31 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1332)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's hard luck or, the fight for right Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 32 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1333)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's protegé or, a helping hand Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 33 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1334)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell on the road or, the show that broke records Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 34 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1335)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's own company or, fun behind the footlights Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 35 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1336)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's fame or, a hard won battle Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 36 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1337)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's college chums or, a stand for clean living Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 37 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898 (Box 65, Folder 1338)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's problem or, between friendship and honor Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 38 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1898-1899 (Box 66, Folder 1339)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's fortune or, a streak of luck Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 39 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1340)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's new comedian or, the rise of a star Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 40 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1341)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's prosperity or, honesty is best Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 41 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1342)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's stage hit or, the art of "making good" Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 42 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1343)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's great scheme; or, head and team work Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 43 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1344)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell in England; or, on his travels Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 44 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1345)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell on the boulevards; or, fun and excitement in France Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 45 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1346)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's duel; or, rough work Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 46 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1347)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's double shot or, the result of daring Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 47 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1348)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's baseball victories or, the king of the diamond Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 48 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1349)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's confidence; or, the boy who held on Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 49 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1350)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's auto; or, fun and frolic on wheels Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 50 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1351)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's fun; or, putting 'em over Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 51 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1352)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's generosity or, kind to friend and foe Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 52 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899 (Box 66, Folder 1353)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's tricks or, almost a magician Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 53 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1899-1900 (Box 66, Folder 1354)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's temptation or, do right, fear nothing Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 54 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 66, Folder 1355)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell on top or hard to beat Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 55 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 66, Folder 1356)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's luck or, a pinch hit Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 56 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 66, Folder 1357)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's mascot; or, a lucky find Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 57 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 66, Folder 1358)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's reward or work and win Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 58 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 66, Folder 1359)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's phantom; or, the mystery Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 59 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1360)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's faith or true to a finish Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 60 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1361)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's victories or, a well-placed hit Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 61 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1362)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's iron nerve or, never say die Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 62 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1363)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell in Kentucky; or, a blue-grass hero Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 63 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1364)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's power; or, right makes might Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 64 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1365)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's shrewdness; or, brain and brawn Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 65 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900 (Box 67, Folder 1366)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's setback; or, true pluck welcomes defeat Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 66 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1900-1901 (Box 67, Folder 1367)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's search or seek and find Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 67 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1368)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's club or, a warm reception Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 68 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1369)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's trust or, never say die Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 69 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1370)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's false friend or, an investment in human nature Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 70 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1371)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's strong arm or, saving an enemy Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 71 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1372)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell as coach or, the effort of his life Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 72 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1373)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's brother or, the greatest triumph of them all Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 73 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1374)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's marvel or, Dick Merriwell's jump ball Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 74 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1375)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's support or, a triple play Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 75 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1376)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell at Fardale or, the wonder of the school Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 76 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 67, Folder 1377)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's glory or, friends and foes Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 77 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 68, Folder 1378)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's promise or, true to his word Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 78 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901 (Box 68, Folder 1379)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's rescue or, undaunted-unafraid Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 79 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1901-1902 (Box 68, Folder 1380)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's narrow escape or, playing the game Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 80 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1381)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's racket or, the boy who would not stoop Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 81 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1382)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's revenge or, coals of fire Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 82 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1383)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's ruse or, a trap for an enemy Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 83 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1384)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's delivery or putting it over Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 84 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1385)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's wonders or, good for a homer Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 85 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1386)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's honor or, the fellow who cut corners Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 86 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1387)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's diamond or, a game worth playing Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 87 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1388)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's winners or, out to clean up Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 88 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1389)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's dash or, fit as a fiddle Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 89 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1390)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's ability or, headwork wins Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 90 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1391)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's trap or the chap who bungled Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 91 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902 (Box 68, Folder 1392)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's defense or, using his brain Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 92 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1902-1903 (Box 68, Folder 1393)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's model or, the boy who led Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 93 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 68, Folder 1394)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's mystery or, working for right Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 94 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 68, Folder 1395)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's backers or, the fellow who balked Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 95 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1396)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's backstop or, a clear head and a good eye Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 96 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1397)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's western mission or, out for a record Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 97 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1398)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's rescue or, a friend in need Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 98 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1399)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's encounter or, fair play Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 99 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1400)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's marked money or, honesty pays Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 100 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1401)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's nomads or, hard to beat Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 101 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1402)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell on the Gridiron or, the knight of the pigskin Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 102 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1403)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's disguise or, a battle with trouble Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 103 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1404)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's test or, sure to win Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 104 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1405)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's trump card or, the go-getter Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 105 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1903-1904 (Box 69, Folder 1406)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's strategy or, with heart and head Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 106 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1407)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's triumph or, a well earned victory Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 107 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1408)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's grit or, the boy who stuck Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 108 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1409)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's assurance or, in his brother's footsteps Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 109 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1410)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's long slide or, taking a chance Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 110 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1411)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's rough deal or, the work of an enemy Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 111 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1412)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's threat or, keeping his word Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 112 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1413)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's persistance or, never say die Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 113 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 70, Folder 1414)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's day or, iron nerve Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 114 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 70, Folder 1415)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's peril or, in the jaws of death Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 115 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 70, Folder 1416)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's downfall or, in a moment of weakness Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 116 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 70, Folder 1417)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's pursuit or, how to win Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 117 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904 (Box 70, Folder 1418)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell abroad or, seeing the world Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 118 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1904-1905 (Box 70, Folder 1419)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell in the Rockies or, the crack of a rifle Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 119 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1420)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's pranks or, livening things up Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 120 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1421)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's pride or, not to be bought Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 121 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1422)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's challengers or, a hard hitter Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 122 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1423)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's endurance or, a square shooter Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 123 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1424)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's cleverness or, fighting his way Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 124 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1425)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Frank Merriwell's marriage or, Inza's happiest day Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 125 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1426)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell, the wizard or, putting them over straight Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 126 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1427)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's stroke or foursquare with the world Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 127 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1428)
  - Author: Standish, Burt L. Title: Dick Merriwell's return or, in spite of luck Series Title: The Merriwell Series Series Number: 128 City: New York Publisher: Street and Smith Date: 1905 (Box 70, Folder 1429)